powerarchiver.com 2017-09-12

# ConeXware, Inc. Privacy Policy | PowerArchiver – ZIP, RAR, ISO for Windows

## ConeXware, Inc. Privacy Policy

We at ConeXware, Inc. are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.

ConeXware has established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit ConeXware’s Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

ConeXware strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, ConeXware intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy. Our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

## Data Collection

ConeXware collects Personal Information when you place an order for one of our products, request support from ConeXware, sign up for a newsletter, or submit a PowerArchiver skin.

When you place an order for one of our products, ConeXware collects Personal Information as required to complete your order. This data includes your name, address, phone number, IP address and credit card details, depending on the payment method selected.

ConeXware sometimes collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a Web site. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your Personal Information with us.

## Data Usage

ConeXware uses Personal Information it collects for the following business purposes, without limitation:

  * maintaining and supporting its products, delivering and providing the requested products/services, and complying with its contractual obligations related thereto (including managing transactions, reporting, invoices, renewals, and other operations related to providing services to a Individual Customer);
  * satisfying governmental reporting, tax, and other requirements (e.g., import/export);
  * storing and processing data, including Personal Information, in computer databases and servers located in the United States;
  * verifying identity (e.g., for online access to accounts);
  * as requested by the Individual Customer;
  * for other business-related purposes permitted or required under applicable local law and regulation, including lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements;
  * and as otherwise required by law.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

When you place an order for PowerArchiver or other ConeXware products, our Web page utilizes “cookies” to uniquely identify your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a Web site. ConeXware uses cookies only to correctly identify you throughout the order process.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will not be able to place an order for a ConeXware product on our Web site.

## Information Sharing

We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of ConeXware, its users or the public.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of ConeXware, Inc., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Choice

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to ConeXware. The notice we intend to provide where ConeXware collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of ConeXware’s Web sites, but you will not be able to place an order or request support.

The PowerArchiver Release Newsletter is an opt-in e-mail newsletter to inform you when ConeXware products have been updated. You will not be contacted for any marketing purposes beyond software update notices. If you wish to unsubscribe, you can do so by visiting the newsletters section. 

## Protecting Your Information

ConeXware takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your Personal Information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

## Accessing, Updating or Deleting Your Information

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, ConeXware wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting ConeXware should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may contact us via e-mail with updates and corrections to your Personal Information.

If you wish to request access to, or review your Personal Information please contact us via e-mail.

Individual Customers have the right to know what Personal Data about them is included in the databases and to ensure that such Personal Information is accurate and relevant for the purposes for which ConeXware collected it. Individual Customers may review their own Personal Information stored in the databases and correct, erase, or block any data that is incorrect, as permitted by applicable law and ConeXware policies. Upon reasonable request and as required by the Privacy Shield principles, ConeXware allows Individual Customers access to their Personal Information, in order to correct or amend such data where inaccurate. Individual Customers may edit their Personal Information by logging into their account profile or by contacting ConeXware by phone or email. In making modifications to their Personal Information, Data Subjects must provide only truthful, complete, and accurate information. To request erasure of Personal Information, Individual Customers should submit a written request via e-mail.

ConeXware will track each of the following and will provide notice to the appropriate parties under law and contract when either of the following circumstances arise: (a) legally binding request for disclosure of the Personal Information by a law enforcement authority unless prohibited by law or regulation;ava or (b) requests received from the Data Subject. If ConeXware receives a request for access to his/her Personal Information from an Individual Customer, then, unless otherwise required under law or by contract with such Individual Customer, ConeXware will refer such Data Subject to the Individual Customer.

ConeXware will endeavor to respond in a timely manner to all reasonable written requests to view, modify, or inactivate Personal Information.

## Children’s Privacy

ConeXware’s Web sites and products are not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Commitment to Privacy

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and ConeXware is committed to meeting these demands. For more information about our practices regarding specific information or services that are not covered in this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework

ConeXware complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. ConeXware has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](hhttps://www.privacyshield.gov/).

ConeXware complies with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. ConeXware has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit [http://2016.export.gov/safeharbor/swiss/index.asp]().

All ConeXware employees who handle Personal Information from Europe and Switzerland are required to comply with the Principles stated in this Policy. ConeXware will maintain, monitor, test, and upgrade information security policies, practices, and systems to assist in protecting the Personal Data that it collects. ConeXware personnel will receive training, as applicable, to effectively implement this Policy.

ConeXware’s accountability for personal information that it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Privacy Shield Principles. In particular, ConeXware remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless ConeXware proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, ConeXware commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Individuals in the European Union with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact ConeXware via email or via phone at: +1 888-302-8800 

For any complaints that cannot be resolved with ConeXware directly, ConeXware has chosen to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the information and advice provided to it by an informal panel of DPAs in relation to such unresolved complaints (as further described in the Privacy Shield Principles). Please contact us to be directed to the relevant DPA contacts. As further explained in the Privacy Shield Principles, a binding arbitration option will also be made available to you in order to address residual complaints not resolved by any other means. ConeXware is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

## PowerArchiver End-User Licensing Agreement (EULA)

For full PowerArchiver End-User Licensing Agreement (EULA), please visit [our Wiki page](https://www.powerarchiver.com/wiki/en:help:additional_information:license). If you have any questions or need more information about our end-user licensing agreement, please contact us.

## Changes to This Policy

This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the Privacy Shield Principles and applicable data protection and privacy laws and principles. We will make employees available of changes to this policy either by posting to our intranet, through email, or other means. We will notify Customers if we make changes that materially affect the way we handle Personal Information previously collected, and we will allow them to choose whether their Personal Information may be used in any materially different manner.

## Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated September 1, 2016
